This is how any properly executed spy exchange should go.
올바로 처리된
스파이 교환이란
어떠해야 하는지
말씀드리죠
You take delivery of the prisoner at the airport.
공항에서 재소자를
인도받게 됩니다
In this case, one Carlo Reni,
이번 경우엔
카를로 레니예요
이탈리아 정보기관 소속으로
A.I.S.E.
Italian A.I.S.E., recently arrested by the FBI
미국 내 스파이 혐의로
최근 FBI에 체포됐죠
for domestic spying.
Yes, Dorothy, allies spy on allies.
네, 맞아요
동맹국의 스파이예요
♬ Airstream Driver ♬
Gomez
아르헨티나의 지정된 교환
장소까지 날아가게 됩니다
You will fly to the designated exchange location in Argentina,
which, by the way, is gorgeous in the summer.
여름이 정말
매력적인 곳이죠
But it's summer here now, meaning-- oh, well, you'll see.
하지만 지금은
여기가 여름이니까
뭐... 가보면 알아요
You will land at a lovely little bit of paradise
착륙할 곳은
허허벌판에 아주 조금은
낙원 같은 곳이에요
in the middle of nowhere,
부에노스아이레스에서
동북 방향으로 일직선 상
90 miles as the crow flies northeast of Buenos Aires.
90마일 떨어진 곳이죠
Perfect for the quiet, off-the-record,
조용하고, 비공식적이고
조금은 살벌한
slightly frosty exchange of foreign operatives.
외국 요원들의
교환 장소론 최고죠
You will then make the exchange just as you made the pickup.
처음에 데려온 대로
그쪽에 인도하면 돼요
You'll be on the ground all of five minutes
착륙해서 단 5분이면
and everyone returns home.
다들 집으로
돌아가게 돼요
Easy-peasy-- that's how it's done.
누워서 떡먹기예요
그렇게 끝나게 됩니다
So, Annie Walker,
그러니까, 애니 워커 양...
have yourself a lovely flight.
즐거운 비행 되시길
THIS IS EXACTLY WHY PEOPLE HATE THE CIA
이러니 사람들이
CIA를 싫어하는 거지
TORTURE, ASSASSINATION- AND NOW-
고문에, 암살에,
이번엔...
이번엔 내가 이렇게 됐네
AND NOW ME
NEXT YOU'LL BE GIVING ME AMERICAN COFFEE
다음 번엔 아메리칸
커피라도 준비해두시죠?
YOU MIGHT AS WELL WATER BOARD ME
물고문이라도
할 수 있을 텐데
ALL I CAN OFFER YOU IS MAYBE A BAG OF PEANUTS
줄 수 있는 건
땅콩뿐이에요
You speak Italian?
이탈리아어를 하는군요?
Interesting.
흥미롭군요
Blonde, Nordic forehead,
금발...
북유럽 계통의 이마...
and lovely mediterranean eyes.
아름다운 지중해 계통
눈동자라니
You have a drop of Italian in you maybe?
이탈리아 혈통이
섞여있지 않나요?
난 미국인이에요
I'm American. But before that.
그전에는요?
Before that, I was American.
그전엔...
미국인이었어요
그럼 당신은...
And you--
darker features, which suggest Southern Italy,
어두운 피부색으로 보자면
남부 이탈리아 출신인데
스파이로선 드물죠
which is rare for a spy, but your dialect is actually Romano.
하지만 사투리로 보아
사실은 로마 출신일 거예요
당연히 로마 출신이죠
남부 혈통은 전혀 없어요
Roma, of course-- there is no south in me.
Below Roma, it's mostly peasants.
로마 남부 지방은
대부분 소작농들이죠
그리고 난
스파이가 아니에요
And I'm not a spy. I'm a journalist. Right.
기자죠
아무렴요
Per favore, signorina,
이것 좀 부탁해요, 아가씨
it is very hard for an Italian to talk without his hands.
손동작 없이 대화하는 건
이탈리아인에겐 제법 힘들어요
Forget it.
꿈도 꾸지 마요
난 내 모든 경력을
I HAVE DEDICATED MY CAREER TO REVEALING JUST THIS SORT OF INJUSTICE -
이런 권리 침해를
폭로하는데 바쳐왔다고요
Maybe I will have some peanuts.
땅콩이라도
괜찮을 거 같네요
ENTRE RIOS PROVINCE ARGENTINA
엔트레 리오스 지방
= 아르헨티나 =
NO SERVICE
통화권 이탈
Sit tight.
가만히 있어요
I'll be back.
다녀올게요
I-I said sit tight.
가만히 있으라고
했잖아요
That's not something I'm good at--sit tight.
가만히 있는 건
내 특기가 아니라서요
Fine. Stay close.
알았어요
가까이 있어요
So how does a woman like you
어쩌다 당신 같은 여자가
end up in a dirty trade like this?
이런 더러운 거래를
하게 됐나요?
Is it God, country, apple cake?
종교 때문에?
국가?
애플 케이크?
- Pie. - Excuse me?
파이요
뭐라고요?
God, country, apple pie.
종교, 국가, 애플 파이
때문이에요
Cake is better.
케이크가 더 나은데
Or panna cotta. Oh!
아니면 파나코타 라든가
God, country, and panna cotta.
종교, 국가, 파나코타...
- Annie. - We're on the ground.
- 애니!
- 착륙했어요
Welcome to sunny Argentina. How was your flight?
화창한 아르헨티나로
가신 걸 축하합니다
비행은 어땠어요?
Talkative. But not hard on the eyes, I'm told.
수다스러웠죠
내가 듣기론 눈은
즐거웠을 거라 하던데?
I didn't notice.
눈치 못 챘네요
Well, of course not. Neither would I.
아무렴 그렇겠죠
나도 마찬가지였을 거예요
Auggie, where's our contact?
오기
접선자는 어디 있어요?
우리만 있어요
We're here alone. Out dealing with weather.
날씨와 싸우고 있어요
Hurricane-force winds in the South Atlantic.
남대서양에
태풍이 왔어요
포클랜드에
우선 착륙했어요
They were forced to land in the Falklands.
The Falklands is 250 miles from here.
포클랜드는 250마일이나
떨어져 있잖아요
잘생긴 이탈리아인과
낙원에 가 있잖아요
Well, you're in paradise with a handsome Italian.
Adapt, overcome, make small talk.
알아서 해요
얘기라도 나눠요
- That's your advice? - Sorry.
- 그게 당신의 충고예요?
- 미안해요
Late night.
잠을 좀 못 자서
Uh, they do expect to be wheels up,
날씨가 좋으면 두 시간 안에
이륙한다고 하네요
hopefully within two hours, weather permitting.
Perfect. Excuse me?
이거야 원
뭐라고요?
I got to go.
끊을게요
Don't be a stranger.
자주 연락해요
Really, Carlo?
이럴 거예요, 카를로?
There's nothing around here for miles.
주변엔 아무것도 없어요
Where do you think you're going?
어디로 가려고요?
What were you gonna do-- run all the way to Buenos Aires?
어쩌려고요?
부에노스아이레스까지
뛰어가려고요?
Ugh, if I have to.
그래야 한다면요
No, no, no, no, no, no. I'm not going back to Italy.
싫어요, 싫어
난 이탈리아로
돌아가지 않을 거예요
There are people there who are very anxious to silence me.
내 입을 막으려는
사람들이 있다고요
You saying there's something worse than the CIA waiting for you? Oh, you don't believe me?
CIA가 기다리는 것보다
안 좋은 일이 있다고요?
믿지 않는군요?
My job is to deliver you safely,
내 일은 당신을 안전하게
인도하는 거예요
난 내 일을
하려는 거예요
and that's what I'm gonna do.
You know, I changed my mind.
There is nothing Italian about you.
생각이 바뀌었어요
당신에겐 이탈리아인 같은
구석이 전혀 없어요
Run.
뛰어요
- What? - Run!
네?
뛰어요!
-==팎읔襟있蹈==-
굶俚캥쏭묩欺構슥직, 拮쐐痰黨庚둡촐
영자막 elderman
www.addic7ed.com
-=팎읔襟俚캥莉=-
럇陋：
叫뚤：
珂쇌菉:kami
Season 2 Episode 4
All the Right Friends
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
줅소큽景묏 뒤랗센뒤4섞
한글번역 에렝아이
디시인사이드 기미갤
서둘러요!
Come on!
You don't have a gun? No.
- 총 없어요?
- 없어요
My agency is no doubt talking to your agency right now,
내 기관에서 당신 기관과
접촉하고 있을 거예요
consulting with the Argentineans
아르헨티나 쪽과 협의해서
and developing a safe and smooth exit for us.
우릴 위해 안전한 탈출구를
만들어줄 거라고요
We'll be fine.
우린 괜찮을 거예요
Come on. Let's go.
서둘러요
어서 가요
This is a disaster.
이건 재앙입니다
This was a favor, Joan. A professional courtesy... I'm aware of that.
우린 호의를
베풀었어요, 조안
동업자 간의
예의였다고요
알고 있어요
부에노스아이레스 // 이탈리아 대사관
개인적인 확약과
그동안의 우정을 믿고!
Based on personal assurances and our long friendship!
부에노스아이레스 // 이탈리아 대사관
잠깐 숨 좀
돌리지그래, 호르헤?
May I suggest you take a breath, Jorge?
싫어, 로마노!
숨 안 돌릴 거야
No, Romano, I will not take a breath, and I take exception to that!
그 반대로 할 거다!
간단한 일이 될 거라고
거듭 다짐받았지
I was made assurances this would be a simple proposition.
Two allies, simple exchange, 30 minutes tops.
두 동맹국 간의
간단한 교환이라고
길어도 30분이라고!
Now I have two international spies
이젠 두 명의 스파이와
암살자를 내 나라에
풀어놓게 됐어!
and an assassin loose in my country!
우리도 그걸 바로잡으려
하고 있어, 호르헤
And we have every intention of rectifying that, Jorge.
- 그래? 어떻게?
- 그렇게 쏘아붙이지 마!
- Really? How? - Please, I won't be snapped at!
We are each in a predicament here.
우린 모두
곤경에 처해있어
맙소사
넌 어떤 곤경인데?
Ay, dios mio! What predicament are you in?
- 여러분, 진정하세요
- 내가 손쓸 방법이 없소, 조안
- Gentlemen, please. - My hands are tied, Joan.
우리나라 국무부와 사안을
공유하는 방법이 있겠지만
It would be one thing if we shared the details
with our departments of state, but I was asked not to.
그러지 말라는
부탁을 받았소
What are you saying, Jorge?
무슨 뜻이죠, 호르헤?
I like my job. I plan to keep it.
난 내 직업이 좋소
그걸 지킬 계획이요
If I catch either operative,
내가 어느 쪽이든
요원을 잡게 되면
스파이 혐의로
체포할 거요
I will arrest them as foreign spies.
감옥에 보낸다는 거군요?
That would mean jail.
- You're being a fool. - I'm sorry, Joan.
- 바보같이 굴지 마
- 미안합니다, 조안
You would do the same if you were in my shoes.
당신도 내 처지라면
똑같이 행동할 거요
Signal's gone.
신호가 끊어졌습니다
Huh. Both signals.
양쪽 다요
That was... Interesting.
이것 참...
흥미롭게 됐네
What do you want to do?
어떻게 할까요?
I have a feeling our domestic colleagues at the FBI
내 직감으론
FBI가 레니에 관해
우리에게 완전히
솔직한 건 아닌 거 같아
haven't been completely forthright with us
about our Mr. Reni. I'm on it.
알아보죠
State? Open a back channel?
국무부요?
교섭 채널을 열까요?
- 아니, 아직
- 국방부에는요?
- No, not yet. - Liaise with the D.O.D.?
I have a different duty for you--you're to see Arthur.
자기에겐 다른 임무가 있어
아서를 만나러 가봐
- We're in the middle of an op. - Mm-hmm.
지금 작전 중인데요
제이가 처리할 거고
And Jai's gonna handle it. Annie's in good hands.
애니에겐 적절히
조치할 거야
Arthur's waiting for you.
아서가 기다리고 있어
나는...
I-I-I--
I had a tryout with A.C. Fiorentina--
AC 피오렌티나에서
입단 테스트 받은 적 있어요
미드필더였죠
yeah, midfielder.
I hurt my knee, and they still wanted to sign me, but--
무릎부상에도 불구하고
그쪽에서...
계속 이동해야 해요
밤은 피하고 싶어요
We need to keep moving. I don't want to lose the light.
- 그렇담 계획이 필요하겠군요
- 계획은 있어요
- Ah, well, we need a plan. - I have a plan.
I don't trust your plan.
- 당신 계획은 신뢰가 안 가요
- 믿어달라고
Well, I don't remember asking you to. I know the perfect place.
부탁한 적도
없는 거 같군요
내가 완벽한 장소를 알아요
I have friends in a little beach town
마르델플라타 해변 마을에
친구들이 있어요
outside Mar del Plata-- Italian.
이탈리아 친구들이죠
Neapolitan, but they're good people.
나폴리 출신이긴 한데
좋은 친구들이에요
She makes a stuffed calamari with squid ink.
오징어와 먹물을 사용해
공예품을 만드는데
Ho-ho! Molto bene.
굉장하죠
우린 이쪽으로 갈 거예요
그게 지침이에요
- We're going this way. - It's really good.
- It's protocol. - Protocol?
지침이요?
맞아요, 지침 덕에 당신도
한 번 목숨을 구했죠
Yeah, which already saved your life once.
Uh-huh, yeah, I realize your boss requires a blind allegiance and slavish devotion, okay?
당신의 보스가
요구하는 게
눈먼 충성심과
맹목적인 헌신인 건 알겠어요
We don't have time for this.
- 이럴 시간 없어요!
- 하지만 내가 아는 건
But I know for a fact that your agency's in league with the people who are trying to kill me.
당신 기관이 날 죽이려는 자들과
결탁했다는 거예요
You understand? You're like a dog with a bone. And I know that I'm absolutely right.
- 정말 끈질기게 구네요!
- 내가 옳다는 걸 알아요
- 옳지 않아요!
- 확실히 알죠
- You're not right. - Absolutely.
이번엔 아니에요
Not this time. Now, please.
이제 갈까요?
어디로요?
To where?
부에노스아이레스의
안전한 장소로요
I'm gonna take you to a safe location in Buenos Aires.
- Oh, okay. - Once there, I check in.
- 그래요, 그래
- 일단 들러서
이상 없다면 당신을
이탈리아 대사관에 넘길 거예요
If everything's okay, I'll take you to the Italian embassy.
Hey, hey, no.
잠깐, 잠깐...
안 돼요
- Yes. - Ah!
돼요!
Nightmare. Don't worry.
걱정 마요
오늘 밤이면
By tonight, you'll be home safe in Italy, and all this will be over.
당신은 안전하게
이탈리아에 있을 거고
그걸로 전부
끝나는 거예요
당신 같은 사람들
밤에 잠은 오나 모르겠군요
I don't know how people like you sleep at night.
CIA 본부
= 버지니아 주 랭리 =
CIA HEADQUATER LANGLEY
I know you felt you owed me, sir,
제게 빚을 졌다고
생각하시는 건 알지만
but a promotion?
승진이요?
This would be a substantial change in your life--
자네 인생에
근본적인 변화가 될 거야
a staff, your own office on the seventh floor.
부하들은 물론이고
7층에 개인 사무실을 갖는 거지
Whoa. A view.
경치 좋겠네요
지위 상승이란
임금 상승이란 뜻이지
A bump in grade means a bump in pay--
a significant one.
눈에 띌 정도지
다음은 주차 공간
얘기가 나올 거 같군요
Next, you're gonna offer me a new parking space.
Two spaces down from mine.
나와 두 칸
떨어진 자리라네
Two spaces south is the D.D.I.
남쪽으로 두 칸이면
D.D.I.죠
He's not going anywhere.
그 자리는 아닐 듯하군요
Two spaces north...
북쪽으로 두 칸이라면...
의회사무국이요?
Office of Congressional Affairs
Office of Congressional Affairs?
We think you'd be perfect.
우린 자네가
적임이라고 생각하네
You want me in O.C.A.? We want you to run O.C.A.
저보고 OCA로 가라고요?
자네보고 OCA를
운영하라는 거지
Charlie's going green badge.
찰리는 은퇴하게 될 거야
He's got kids to put through college.
대학에 보낼
아이들이 있거든
Plus, it's time for newer blood, younger blood.
게다가 지금은 새로운 피,
젊은 피가 필요한 시기야
그 말은...
Well, that would mean--
맞아, 오기
Yes, Auggie.
You'd be overt.
자네 이름을
드러내는 거지
I could never go in the field again. Yeah, that's right.
다시는 현장으로
돌아갈 수 없겠군요
그래, 맞아
Once you step in front of the cameras, it's--
일단 카메라 앞으로
발을 옮기면...
I remember when I did it.
내 기억이 떠오르는군
It was a big step.
아주 큰 발걸음이지
You'd be one of three public faces for the CIA--
CIA에서 공개된 얼굴
셋 중 하나가 되는 거야
the D.C.I., me, and you.
중앙정보국장, 나
그리고 자네
뭐 잘못했나 걱정하면서
올라왔는데
Here I thought I was in trouble.
Oh, this is a hell of an opportunity-- a career maker.
이건 굉장한 기회야
대단한 경력으로
가는 길이지
And honestly...
그리고 솔직히...
자넬 현장에서
끌어올리는 건 아니지
We're not exactly pulling you from the field.
The D.C.I. and I agree.
기관장과 나는 동의했다네
우리 모두 자네가 이 일에
적임자라고 생각하네
We both think you are the right man for the job.
I'm speechless. Well, you'd have to work on that.
- 말문이 막히네요
- 그 점은 해결해야 할 거야
You can't be speechless on this job.
말을 안 하곤
할 수 없는 일이니까
- When? - You'd start next week.
언제죠?
다음 주에 시작이야
So you need to give it some serious thought.
그러니 그동안
심사숙고해보게
Carlo Reni was arrested by the FBI two days ago
카를로 레니는 이틀 전
FBI에 체포됐어요
워싱턴에서 토지관리국의
뒤를 캐낸 혐의였죠
for reading the trash at the Bureau of Land Management here in D.C.
He said he was investigating a story for--
자기 말론 취재를 하던...
위장신분을 고수했다는 건
나도 알아
I know. I know. He stuck to his cover. I know this.
내가 모르는
사항을 말해줘
Tell me what I don't know.
The FBI had him all of five hours before the Italian A.I.S.E. offered up a trade.
FBI에선 이탈리아 AISE가
거래를 제안하기 전까지
레니를 고작 5시간 억류했어요
이건 알고 있었어요?
Did you know that? No.
아니
Which means, of course--
그 말은 즉...
AISE가 레니의 진짜 신분을
드러냈다는 거지
His own agency blew his cover.
- He knows something. - What?
- 알고 있는 게 뭔가 있군요
- 그게 뭘까?
He said he was only in the country for five days before he was arrested.
체포되기 전까지 미국에
닷새 체류했다고 했어
- Where was he before that? - A lot of traveling--
그전엔 어디 있었지?
여행을 많이 했어요
주로 남미에서
위장신분대로 행동했죠
mostly South America, working his cover.
그전엔 중동 지역을
방문했네요
Before that, some Middle East visits. He was kicked out of Iran for publishing articles
발행한 기사와 관련해서
이란에서 추방당했어요
"Libelous and unfavorable to the government."
"정부에 대한 비방과 비판"
이었군요
What does Persia House say? That he was kicked out for his story, ostensibly.
이란 쪽 입장은?
표면적으로는 레니의 기사
때문이라고 했어요
레니를 감시 명단에
올려놓았고요
They have him on a watch list.
Get Genaro. I want a face-to-face.
제나로와 약속 잡아줘
직접 만나봐야겠어
Auggie. Joan.
오기?
조안?
Good meeting? Interesting meeting.
회의는 즐거웠어?
흥미로운 회의였죠
What can I do?
전 뭘 할까요?
I want confirmation that there is a jet on the ground in the Falklands.
포클랜드에 실제로 착륙한
비행기가 있는지 확인해줘
우릴 갖고 노는 게
아닌지 알아내야 해
I want to know whether or not we're being played.
I can do that.
그러죠
And someone please find out who the opposition is.
우리 상대가 누군지도
누가 알아봐줘
현장에 암살자가 있는데
누군지 알고 싶어
If we have a hitter in the field, I want to know who it is.
여기가 당신이 불쌍한 소작농의
차를 훔칠 장소겠군요
And this is probably where you steal
some hapless peasant's vehicle, his only worldly possession-- typical.
농부의 유일한 재산일 텐데
- 뻔하죠
- 사실은...
Actually, this is where I buy it.
차를 구입할 장소예요
Buenos dias!
안녕하세요!
하지만 훔쳤을 수도
있잖아요
But you would have stolen it.
Let me drive. I know the way.
내가 운전하죠
길을 알아요
In Italy, a woman never drives.
이탈리아에선
여자가 운전하지 않아요
운전은 남자죠
The man drives.
We're not in Italy.
여긴 이탈리아가 아니에요
Fine.
좋아요
Get us lost. We're not lost.
길을 잃겠군요
잃지 않아요
It's only a matter of time.
시간문제일 뿐이에요
Auggie?
오기?
Got a signal, I think,
신호를 찾은...거 같아요
at least that's what N.G.A. tells me, but they might be playing with me.
적어도 지리 정보국에
따르면 그런데
어쩌면 저를 가지고
노는 걸 수도 있어요
Officially, it's in customs' hold.
공식적으론 세관
관리하에 있어요
승객과 승무원은
그대로 탑승 중이고요
Passengers and crew are still aboard.
Can we get eyes on the ground? Working on it.
현지 화면을
받을 수 있어?
알아보고 있어요
What about Genaro at the Italian embassy? I'm making arrangements.
이탈리아 대사관의
제나로는?
약속을 조정하고 있어요
Word is, he'd like to speak with you, too.
제나로도 당신을
만나고 싶다고 하네요
Good.
좋아
- Anything on our hitter? - One possible--
- 암살자에 관해선?
- 가능성이 하나 있어요
a Helmut Drum.
헬무트 드럼
He arrived in Buenos Aires on a flight from London yesterday morning--
어제 아침 런던발 비행기로
부에노스아이레스에 도착했어요
former Chechen separatist, noted involvement in death squads,
전 체첸 분리주의자였고
암살단에 참여한 걸로
알려져 있죠
ties to the usual unsavory suspects,
부도덕한 용의자들과
연계되어 있어요
mostly Eastern Europe.
주로 동유럽 쪽에서
활동했고요
It's believed he's independent.
지금은 독립한 걸로
알려졌어요
유럽과의 유대와 백인 외모라면
특정 시장에선 인기 상품이죠
European ties, anglo appearance makes him a good commodity in certain markets.
이젠 아르헨티나에
있는 거군
Now he's in Argentina. He fits Annie's description.
애니가 설명한
인상착의와 맞아요
I profiled this guy for the U.K. desk.
영국 지부에 있을 때
이 자를 프로파일 했었어요
He is not a true believer anymore. He is all about the money.
이젠 정치적 광신자가 아니에요
돈만을 위해 움직이죠
He's the real deal. Let's give Annie a heads-up.
위험 인물이에요
애니에게 주의를 주자고
Already tried. Can't reach her.
해봤어요
연락이 안 돼요
- Try again. - Yep.
- 다시 해봐
- 네
내가 운전했으면
이런 일은 없어요
This wouldn't happen if you let me drive.
I would kill for a macchiato.
마끼아또 마시고
싶어 죽겠어요
Speaking of which...
말이 나와서 말인데
Any idea who wants you dead?
당신이 죽길 바라는
사람이 누군지 알겠어요?
- Now you want to know? - Might be helpful.
- 이제야 궁금한 모양이군요
- 알면 도움이 될지도 모르죠
People in your line of work, maybe people you know.
당신 같은 일을 하는 사람이죠
아는 사람일지도 몰라요
I don't know people like that.
그런 사람은
모르는데요
And I don't work with people like that.
그런 사람들과
일하지도 않아요
You keep saying you're not a spy,
계속 스파이가 아니라고
우겨도 좋지만
and yet consider the circumstances.
상황을 좀 생각해요
몇몇 정당들을 불쾌하게
했다는 건 인정하죠
I admit to making certain parties unhappy.
It's the nature of my work. The only thing we have in common--
내 일의 본질이니까요
그게 우리 사이의
유일한 공통점이에요
I'm not the one with an assassin after him.
암살자가 쫓는 건
내가 아니에요
The free press has its enemies in your country and mine.
자유언론의 적은
어느 나라에서나 있죠
I'll give you one thing, Carlo. Whatever you are, you talk a good game.
한 가지만
말할게요, 카를로
당신 정체가 뭐든
말은 그럴싸해요
I'll give you that.
인정할게요
Alternator belt.
교류발전기 벨트였어요
It's not pretty, but it'll hold.
그다지 좋진 않은데
버틸 순 있을 거예요
Another thing I'm not-- mechanical.
제 특기가 아닌
또 한 가지가, 기계죠
If I found you a macchiato,
마끼아또 한 잔이면
you think that might jog your memory
누가 우릴 쫓는지
기억날 거 같아요?
about who's after us?
Maybe.
어쩌면요
하지만 카라멜이나
휘핑크림은 안 돼요
But no caramel or whipped cream.
It's coffee. It's not an apple pie.
마끼아또는 커피지
애플 파이가 아니라고요
Look, Internet-- I could check my blog.
인터넷이 된다네요
블로그를 확인해야겠어요
Classic.
훌륭해요
완벽한 기자 위장이군요
Perfect journo cover.
블로그에 아무것도
없잖아요
We both know there's nothing on your blog.
그럴까요?
확인해봐요
No? Let's go.
I'll show you what I've dedicated my life to,
내 인생을 어디에
바쳤는지 보여드리죠
why people follow my work, even Americans.
왜 미국인을 포함한
많은 사람들이 날 쫓는지도요
얼마나 많은
아르헨티나인이
How many people in Argentina do you think
지금 당신 블로그에
접속해 있을 거 같아요?
are logged on to your blog right now?
My guess is only you.
내 짐작으론
당신 하나예요
I happen to have a, uh, devoted following
티에라 델 푸에고에 날 열렬히
지지하는 사람들이 있어요
in Tierra del Fuego.
우릴 쫓는 사람이
감시 중일 거예요
Whosever after us will be watching it. As soon as you log on, they'd have us.
로그인하는 즉시
발각되기 때문에...
So...
No.
안 돼요
And as far as the Argentinean authorities are concerned,
그리고 아르헨티나
관계 당국이 알기론
you and I are both spies.
우린 둘 다
스파이라고요
They find us, we go to jail.
그들이 우릴 찾으면
우린 감옥에 가는 거예요
Jail doesn't scare me.
감옥은 두렵지 않아요
It's a censored press that scares me.
검열받는 언론이 두렵죠
Come on.
가요
Treat time.
간식 시간이에요
Gracias.
고마워요
Ooh! Milanesa!
밀라니사!
달걀, 빵, 럼주 조금
빠르게 튀겨내면
Eggs, crumbs, little rub, quick fry.
Argentine beef-- the second-best in the world.
아르헨티나의 쇠고기는
세계에서 두 번째예요
It's one of the reasons I love Argentina.
아르헨티나를 사랑하는
이유 중 하나죠
Frankly, I prefer parrillada.
솔직히 난
빠리쟈다가 더 좋아요
Oh, parrillada. Bene.
빠리쟈다!
괜찮죠
마끼아또예요
Macchiato.
Marked.
찍었어요
마끼아토는 이탈리아 어로
"점찍다"는 뜻
I know the saucer's not heated,
받침까지 데우진 않았지만
but when in Argentina...
여긴 아르헨티나니까...
You like me.
날 좋아하는군요?
I can tell.
알아챌 수 있어요
No, we have what we Romans call "simpatia."
아뇨, 우리 로마인들은
이런 걸 "연민"이라고 불러요
당신도 그걸 느끼고 있죠?
You feel it, too, yes?
누구나 가지고
있는 공간이에요
It's the common space,
the mortar between the bricks, the words between the words--
벽돌 사이의 몰타르
단어 사이의 단어
courage...
용기
Passion, principles.
열정
원칙
Simpatia.
연민
This is... maybe you and me.
그것이...
어쩌면 우리 사이에
있는 거죠
당신은 내가...
You are either the best operative
여태껏 만난 요원 중에
최고이거나
I have ever seen or the absolute worst.
당연코 최악이에요
I can't make up my mind.
쉽게 결정할 수가 없네요
난 당신 일 같은 건
할 수 없어요
I couldn't do what you do.
I trust people. They trust me.
난 사람들을 믿죠
사람들도 날 믿고요
It's how I do my job. Me too.
그게 내 일을
하는 방법이죠
나도 마찬가지예요
People trust me. Lots of people trust me, in fact.
사람들은 날 믿어요
사실 아주 많은
사람들이 날 믿죠
CIA에서 당신에게
그 "신뢰"로 뭘 하랍니까?
And what does the CIA ask you to do with this "trust"?
Today they're having me protect and deliver a foreign operative.
오늘은 내게 외국 요원을
보호하고 인도하라고 했죠
You know what?
티타임 끝났어요
이제 가요
Treat time's over. Let's go.
You know what, Carlo? You have us wrong.
그거 알아요, 카를로?
당신은 우릴 잘못 봤어요
You got me wrong.
날 잘못 봤다고요
I need to, um, use the...
나는... 저길 좀...
without assistance.
도움 없이요
Oh, no.
아뇨, 어머니 무덤을
걸고 맹세하는데
I-I promise on my mother's grave, I will not run away.
도망치지 않을게요
Ah! Scusa.
실례
Scusa. Grazie.
고마워
Your mom's not really dead, is she?
어머니가 실은
돌아가시지 않았죠?
Policia federal.
경찰이군요
That's a good thing, yes? That's not a good thing.
잘 된 거죠?
아니에요
What are they doing here? Hmm, it's Argentina.
여기서 뭘하는 걸까요?
여긴 아르헨티나니까
아마도...
They're probably--
Get down!
숙여요!
What are you doing?
뭐하는 거예요?
Carlo, I need you to be quiet right now.
카를로, 지금은 조용히
해줬으면 좋겠어요
Grab something. What?
꽉 잡아요
뭐라고요?
And this is where I'm not supposed to argue?
내가 끼어들어선
안 되는 일이에요?
Do you see him?
쫓아와요?
No. Maybe policia got him.
아뇨, 경찰이
붙잡은 지도 모르죠
그렇진 않을 거예요
Oh, I doubt it.
How did he find us?
어떻게 우릴 찾은 거죠?
I don't know.
모르겠어요
Here you go.
여기 있습니다
무척 걱정이에요, 로마노
I'm very worried, Romano. I'm exposed here.
- 여기선 노출되어 있어요
- 물론이죠, 나도 공감해요
Joan, of course, you know I'm sympathetic.
쉬운 일이라 생각했던 계획이
재앙이 돼버렸어요
This piece of cake we planned has turned into a disaster for me.
Keeping this on the sly has been a total mistake.
계속 은밀히 해둔 게
큰 실수였어요
I can't do it anymore. I have to go vertical with this, Romano.
더는 어쩔 수 없어요
윗선에 말해야겠어요
네? 그럼 끝장이에요
What? Let's not lose our heads, dear.
모르겠어요
혼란스러워요
I don't know. I'm very confused.
I need to tell my boss. I need to tell the State Department.
상관에게 말해야 해요
국무부에도 말해야 하고요
윗선에 말하지 않으면
난 끝이에요
I have to read them in on this, or it will be my ass...
In a very nasty and very permanent way.
아주 끔찍하고
아주 영구적으로요
조안, 내 말 잘 들어요
Joan, listen to me.
I won't let you go down. I promise.
내가 그렇게 두지
않을 거예요
약속하죠
We are all on the hook here, dear, not just you.
우린 모두 이 일에
묶여 있어요
우리는 함께 가는 거예요
We are in this together. I don't know about that.
그건 잘 모르겠군요
Okay, look, I understand your concern.
좋아요, 보세요
뭘 걱정하는지 알아요
Just give me a few hours.
몇 시간만 더 줘요
전부 잘 해결될 거예요
It's all going to work out.
당신 생각이 그렇다면
그런 거겠죠
I guess, if you think it'll work.
Good.
좋아요
제나로가 넘어갔어
Genaro fell for it. He's dirty. We're being played. I'm sure of it.
다른 속셈이 있어
우린 놀아났던 거야
확실해
Pleading, "We're in this together"?
"우린 함께 가는 거예요"
라니...
Right.
뻔해
Actually, there was a problem.
사실 문제가 있었어요
Annie busted through a police barricade. There's a countrywide A.P.B. out on her.
애니가 경찰 저지선을
돌파했어요
아르헨티나 전역에
지명수배가 내려졌어요
What do you want me to do?
어떻게 할까요?
Change directives.
명령을 변경해
Let's move on an extraction.
구출 단계로 넘어가자고
Take your clothes off.
옷 벗어요
Uh, pardon me?
뭐, 뭐라고요?
There's no way that hitter could have known where we were.
암살자가 우리 위치를
알아낼 방법이 없었어요
Take 'em off.
벗어요
For heaven sakes. I'll step outside.
맙소사, 밖에 있을게요
No, that--ah.
아니...
When you were in custody, did anyone come to visit you?
구속됐을 때
찾아온 사람 없나요?
Uh, yes.
있어요, 대사관에서
누가 찾아왔었죠
One person from the embassy. So what?
그게 왜요?
Who? He didn't say his name.
누구요?
이름을 말해주지 않았어요
Did anyone else have access
당신이 있던 장소나
당신 물건에
to where you were or your things?
접근할 수 있었던
다른 사람은요?
No.
없어요
You didn't check your clothes.
옷도 확인해보지 않았군요
No. Why would I?
네, 그걸 왜 해요?
That's how the hitter found us.
이것 때문에 암살자가
우릴 찾아낸 거예요
He must have planted it on you when you met.
당신과 만났을 때
심어둔 게 틀림없어요
Get dressed. We're on foot from here.
옷 입어요
여기서부턴 걸어갈 거예요
Are you kidding?
장난해요?
"Get dressed. Take it off.
옷 입어라, 벗어라
뛰어라, 와라
멈춰라, 저리 가라
Run. Come here. Stop. Go there."
또요?
Again? It's for your own good.
당신을 위한 거예요
네, 그럼요
아무렴요
Yeah, sure. Whatever.
당신은 분명 이탈리아 남자와
사귀어본 적 없을 거예요
You know, I bet you never had an Italian boyfriend.
한번 사귀면 내 인생이
영원히 바뀌겠죠
Oh, which would change my life forever, no doubt.
그렇게 농담하지만
아무 여자에게나 물어봐요
You joke, but you ask any woman, she'll tell you.
알려줄 거예요
We know things. You, however-- you're a lost cause.
우린 비결이 있죠
하지만 당신은
가망이 없죠
당신 정말 이런 사람이에요?
- Are you really this person? - Eh.
I'm trying to keep us alive,
난 살아보려고 발버둥인데
당신 관심은 내 남자친구예요?
and you're interested in my boyfriends?
난 당신 애정 생활을
도와주려고...
Well, I'm trying to help your love life-- You want to help me?
날 돕고 싶어요?
누가 당신을 죽이려는지 말해요
Tell me who's trying to kill you.
그게...
Well--
여자가 알아도
되는 문제라면요
Unless a woman shouldn't know these things. Look, I mean--
I think it's about a story I've been working on...
내가 쓰고 있는 기사
때문인 거 같아요
about the O.C.U. The Italian oil conglomerate?
- OCU에 관한 기사죠
- 이탈리아 석유 대기업이요?
Yes, exactly, and the Italian government. It's a conspiracy?
바로 그거예요
이탈리아 정부도 관계됐죠
음모예요?
My sources are connected to certain government officials.
내 정보원들은 특정
공무원들과 연결되어 있어요
It's about the oil rigs here in South America.
남미에서의 석유 시추에
관한 내용이죠
I want to get you to a safe house.
당신을 안전가옥으로
데려가야겠어요
BUENOS AIRES ARGENTINA
부에노스아이레스
= 아르헨티나 =
They say, "Follow the money."
돈을 쫓아가라고 했어요
돈을 쫓다 보니
여기까지 온 거예요
Well, I followed the money, and here I am.
그들은 내 출판이
임박했다는 걸 알아요
They know I'm close to publishing.
I have corroboration-- how they bribed and extorted
나에겐 증거가 있어요
산호르헤 유전을 얻기 위한
뇌물과 갈취에 관한 거죠
to get their share of the San Jorge oil fields.
They want to stop me. They need to stop me.
그들은 날 멈추고 싶어 해요
날 멈춰야만 하죠
I am not a spy. I'm a writer.
난 스파이가 아니에요
난 기자예요
I've been working on this story for two years.
난 이 기사에
2년을 매달렸어요
Someone wants me back in Italy to--
누군가 날 이탈리아로
송환하려 해요
to stop me from publishing.
출판을 막기 위해서요
이탈리아 대사관으론
가지 않는 게 좋겠어요
The Italian embassy may not be the place to go. Finally.
이제야 겨우...
But we can't go to the U.S. embassy either.
- 미국 대사관으로도 못 가요
- 왜요?
- Why? - It's complicated.
상황이 복잡해요
Yeah? Where are you?
네?
- 어디야?
- 도심이에요
- We're in the city. - You are not safe.
넌 안전하지 않아
The local authorities have your descriptions. Not surprising.
지역 경찰이
네 인상착의를 알고 있어
놀랍진 않네요
네 탈출 경로를
모색하고 있어
We're working on an extraction.
이탈리아 대사관으론
가지 마
You are not to go to the Italian embassy.
- 알겠어?
- 네
Understood? Yeah.
I-I already figured that out.
그 점은 이미
알아냈어요
Are either of you injured? No, we're good.
부상당한 사람은?
아뇨, 저희 괜찮긴 한데
The package may not be what we thought it was.
이송자가 우리가 생각했던
사람이 아닌 거 같아요
Well, I don't think anyone is who we think they are.
어느 쪽도 우리가 생각한
사람들이 아닐 거야
Either way, your safety is what's important.
어쨌든, 중요한 건
네 안전이야
Auggie's working on a possible exit. "Possible"?
오기가 가능한 탈출구를
알아보고 있어
"가능한"이요?
Highly probable, though still in the formative stages.
아직 형성 단계지만
거의 확실한 장소예요
I need you to get
부두에 US프레지던츠 라인
집하장까지 이동해요
to the U.S. President's Line terminal at the wharf.
U.S. President's line at Buenos Aires or La Cotta?
US프레지던츠 라인이요
부에노스아이레스요?
아니면 라코타요?
Buenos Aires, berth 28.
부에노스아이레스
28번 정박지예요
도착하면 더 자세한
정보를 알려줄 테니
I'll have more information when you get there. Just get there and be safe.
일단 가요
조심하고요
알아둬야 할 일이
한 가지 더 있어
And there's another detail you need to be aware of.
애니, 카를로의 정보원
두 명이 지난 24시간 안에
Annie, we've discovered that two of Carlo's contacts have turned up dead
죽었다는 사실을
알아냈어요
in the past 24 hours. Both were employed by O.C.U.
모두 OCU의
직원이었어요
OCU에 관한 기사를 쓰고
있단 얘길 들었어요
He told me he's working on a story about O.C.U.
Their names are Rinaldo and Vasquez.
정보원의 이름은 리날도와
바스케즈예요
Keep your head down. Get to the wharf.
이목 끌지 말고
부두까지 가
We'll get you out.
벗어나게 해줄게
What?
왜요?
Rinaldo and Vasquez-- does that mean anything?
리날도와 바스케즈라고 하면
떠오르는 거 있어요?
Two of my sources. Why?
내 정보원들이에요
왜요?
죽었어요
They're dead.
We have to get to the wharf.
부두까지 가야 해요
My agency's gonna try and get us out of here.
기관에서 우릴 벗어나게
해주려 하고 있어요
But, but--
하지만...
Carlo.
카를로
Carlo, I'm sorry.
카를로, 정말 유감이에요
I know this is hard, but we have to move. I'm responsible.
힘들다는 거 알지만
우린 가야 해요
난 책임이 있어요
They put their faith in me, and now they're dead.
날 믿어준
두 사람이 죽었어요
The police are looking for us.
경찰이 우릴 찾고 있어요
당신이 잡히거나 감옥에 가면
전부 물거품이 된다고요!
It'll all be for nothing if you get caught and go to jail.
We have to move, now.
지금 가야 해요
이거 뭐하는 거죠?
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE
MY BOYFRIEND - OFFICER - HE'S ALWAYS MAKING ME PLAY HESEKINKY GAMES-
제 남자친구예요, 경관님
이런 별난 장난치는 걸
좋아해서요
IT'S STUPID, I KNOW-
엉뚱한 짓이었죠
알아요
미친 여자예요
어떻게 좀 해주세요
THIS WOMAN IS CRAZY- GET HER AWAYFROM ME.
MY BOYFRIEND IS PLAYING A TRICK ON YOU.
남자친구가 장난치는 거예요
Sorry.
미안해요
편집장과 만날 수 있을까요?
I need to talk to the editor, please. Claro que si.
네, 그럼요
Annie, how-- how did you know? Where else would a writer go?
애니, 어떻게 알았어요?
기자라면 어딜 가겠어요?
A writer?
기자요?
Look, we are still in danger, and I am still responsible for you.
우린 여전히 위험하고
난 여전히 당신에게
책임이 있어요
- When did you decide that-- - We don't have time for this.
언제 그렇게 결정...
시간이 없어요
탈출 지점까지 가야 해요
We need to get to the extraction point.
I am glad. I really am, but I have to do this.
믿어줘서 기뻐요
정말 기쁘지만
난 이걸 해야만 해요
No, you need to trust me.
아뇨, 당신은
날 믿어야 해요
난 당신을 믿어요
대부분의 경우에는요
I do trust you... Mostly.
But I trust this too.
하지만 난 이것도 믿어요
Look, if I'm going to get killed, Annie,
내가 만약 죽게
된다면, 애니
which at this point is fairly probable,
지금으로선 죽을
확률도 제법 높죠
then I have to get my story out.
그렇다면 난...
기사를 내보내야만 해요
I have to.
반드시 내보내야 해요
난 약속을 했어요
I made promises, and I want to keep those promises.
그 약속을 지키고 싶어요
How do you know they'll print it? I don't.
그걸 발행할지는
어떻게 알고요?
몰라요
But it's not the battles won, Annie.
하지만 이건 전쟁을 이기기
위함이 아니에요
It's the battles waged.
전쟁을 수행하기 위함이죠
당신은 이해할 수
있을 거예요
You can understand that...
당신이 내가 생각하는
사람이 맞다면요
If you are who I think you are.
Make it quick.
서둘러요
You think I have an ulterior motive?
내게 숨겨진 이유가
있다고 생각하나?
Frankly, yes.
솔직히 그렇습니다
We all have motives.
"누구나 이유가 있다"
We're told that in our training, to expect it.
그걸 예상하라고
훈련 받았죠
내 주변 상황 때문에
내 이유가 의심스러운 건가?
You think mine are suspect due to my circumstances?
No, sir. Due to my circumstances.
아닙니다
제 주변 상황 때문이죠
국장님은 홍보전을
치르고 있는데
You're in a public relations battle,
and I'm the feel-good hit of the summer.
저는 잘 먹히는
한방이니까요
That's ballsy, Auggie. Good for you.
배짱 한번 좋군, 오기
훌륭해
I have my reasons, sure.
나에겐 물론
내 이유가 있지
And, yes, I am fighting for my career.
내 지위를 위해
싸우고 있는 것도 맞아
So what? It's irrelevant.
그래서?
상관없는 일이야
There's never a clean game board, Auggie, never.
깨끗한 게임판이란 없어
오기, 절대 없지
Gets more complicated the higher you climb.
오르면 오를수록
복잡해질 뿐이야
Up or down, yes or no.
오르거나 내리거나
예 혹은 아니오
Your decision, your terms.
자네의 결정이고
자네의 말이야
To hell with me or what I may or may not need.
나나 내가 필요로 하는 건
신경 쓸 필요 없어
And I wouldn't worry about me too much if I were you.
내가 자네라면
그렇게 걱정하지 않을 거야
난 아직 이빨 빠진
호랑이가 아니야
I still have a few teeth in my head.
Question--
질문이 있습니다
who would I answer to?
누구에게 대답하면 되죠?
The D.C.I. and me.
기관장이나 내게
말하면 되지
And what about...Perks?
특전은 뭐가 있을까요?
What do you have in mind?
무얼 생각하나 있나?
Say I wanted an extraction in a foreign country.
외국에서 탈출 지점을
확보하고 싶은데요
I thought you were gonna ask for a wet bar.
개인 바라도 설치해달라고
할 줄 알았더니
His people are working on the same story.
여기서도 같은 기사를
쓰고 있어요
He's got a reporter in the San Jorge Gulf, and I also got a name.
산호르헤 만에
기자를 파견해놨어요
이름도 알아냈어요
I know who visited me when I was in custody.
구속됐을 때
찾아온 사람 말이에요
누구예요?
- Who? - Genaro.
제나로
로마노 제나로예요
Romano Genaro. He's Italian intelligence.
이탈리아 기관
소속이잖아요
He gets a cut on any oil extracted--
제나로가 채굴된 석유의
일부를 챙겨요
potentially millions.
잠재적으로
수백만이에요
I knew I was making someone in the government unhappy,
내가 정부의 누군가를 불편하게
한다는 건 알고 있었어요
someone pulling strings. I didn't know until now.
누군가 영향력을 행사해왔는데
여태까지는 누군지 몰랐죠
He's in for a big surprise.
기사가 발행되면
크게 당황하겠죠
What's the best way to the wharf?
부두까지 갈
좋은 방법 있어요?
Genaro's our man.
제나로의 짓이었어요
He's been assisting the Italian oil conglomerate O.C.U.
이탈리아의 석유 대기업
OCU를 도와주며
석유 계약을
강요하고 있었어요
And coercing oil leases.
Carlo Reni's investigations were about to uncover that
카를로 레니의 취재는
그 사실을 적발하고
이름을 밝힐 단계까지
나아갔어요
and name names. That's why Genaro was so anxious
그래서 제나로가
이 일을 공식 채널에
올리지 않으려 한 거죠
to keep this off the official channels. So much for professional courtesy.
그것 참 대단한
동업자 간의 예의군요
Reni is not a spy.
레니는 스파이가 아니에요
But, Joan, this doesn't change the facts on the ground.
조안, 그렇다고 현지사정이
바뀌진 않아요
호르헤?
Jorge--
당신 요원은
경찰 저지선을 뚫고
Your operative crashed through a police checkpoint
지역 경찰을
폭행했어요
and assaulted a local policeman. I'm bringing her in.
난 잡아들일 거예요
Do not threaten me. This is my operative at risk.
날 협박하지 마요
위험에 처한 건 내 요원이에요
또한 우리가 하는 일이란
바로 이런 거죠, 조안
And this is the business we're in, Joan.
You do your job.
당신은 당신 일을 해요
I'll do mine.
난 내 일을 하겠소
Jorge, sometime, somewhere...
호르헤...
언젠가, 어디선가
우리가 다시
함께 일하게 됐을 때
We will have future business.
Do not think for a minute that your harming
당신이 내 요원에게
해를 가한 것이
우리의 관계에
영향이 없을 거라고
one of my people will not have a deep impact
조금도 기대하지 마요
on our relationship.
BUENOS AIRES WHARF
부에노스아이레스 부두
Annie, what's he doing here?
애니? 저 자가
어떻게 온 거죠?
Someone at the newspaper must have tipped him off.
신문사의 누군가가
귀뜸했을 거예요
What?
네?
수갑 풀게요
What? I'm gonna uncuff you.
Give me your word. Yeah.
약속해요
알았어요
I want you to stay right here, and I'll be back.
여기서 기다려요
바로 돌아올게요
안 돼요, 잠깐만
뭘 하려는 거예요?
No, wait, wait, wait. What are you going to do?
Keep you safe.
당신을 지키려는 거예요
당신 기관 사람들은
오지 않아요
Your people are not coming.
- They're coming. - No.
- 올 거예요
- 아니에요!
일이 복잡하게 되는 순간
The minute things became complicated, you became dispensable.
당신은 버림받은 거예요
It's easier to just let us die. You're wrong.
우릴 죽게 내버려두는 게
더 쉬우니까요
틀렸어요
The people I work for don't think of me as dispensable,
나와 일하는 사람들은
나를 버려도 된다고
생각하지 않아요
or you.
당신도요
They'll be here.
올 거예요
Come on.
따라와요
- You okay? - Uh-huh.
괜찮아요?
우릴 태우러 온 거예요
That's our ride.
We have a visual on them.
시야에 들어왔다
Extraction team has them in sight.
구출팀의 시야 안에
들어왔습니다
현장에 지역 경찰이 있다
Local police are on the scene.
Standing by.
대기하라
칭찬해주지
My compliments...
eluding my men, staying alive.
내 요원들을 따돌리고
살아남고
But this is the end of the road.
하지만 이걸로 끝이야
이걸로 됐어
Enough.
Miss, you and Mr. Reni will leave my country
당신과 레니는...
내 나라에서
가능한 한 빨리 나가
as quickly as possible.
Tell Joan I look forward to our next time.
조안에게 전해
다음 번을 기대하겠다고
I will.
그러죠
고마워요
송수신 상태 양호
전원 탑승했다
We're 555, whole package on board.
Over and out.
통신 끝
Mr. Genaro, would you care to add anything
제나로 씨
아르헨티나에서 미국 요원을
공격한 것에 대한
to your statement regarding the attack on a U.S. operative in Argentina?
당신의 진술에 덧붙일
말씀이 있습니까?
He offered you the job, didn't he?
국장이 네게
자리를 제안했지?
Looks like you're his boy now.
이젠 네가 국장의
심복이 된 거 같군
Good luck with that.
행운을 빌지
* Count the steps... *
나는...
- I, um... - * from where I am *
자기 잘못을
인정할 줄 알아요
Big enough to eat my words.
난 고향에 가서
I'm going home,
and I'm publishing because of the CIA.
기사를 발행할 거예요
CIA 덕분이죠
Eh, I may have to rethink some of my positions.
하지만 몇 가지에 대한
내 견해는 재고해야겠군요
Italian men are impressive. Come to Italy now.
이탈리아 남자들은
정말 인상깊네요
이탈리아로 와요
I'll show you Roma. My mother will cook.
로마 구경시켜 줄게요
우리 어머니가
요리해주실 거예요
Your mother?
당신의 어머니가요?
Well, I'm a good Italian son.
난 착한 이탈리아
아들이에요
Maybe another time.
다음에 기회가 된다면요
* I know you're never gonna... *
* I would have let you leave *
안녕
Ciao.
* I would have let you leave *
♬ Static Waves ♬
Andrew Belle
* the static waves across the screen *
* define this notion *
* back and forth and in between *
"이탈리아 공무원이 석유 부패의
덫에 걸리다" - 카를로 레니
* like my emotion *
* And I know you're never gonna understand *
* and won't you slow down-- *
새로운 메시지가
하나 있습니다
One new message.
잘 다녀왔어요?
Welcome home, stranger.
Look, find me when you get a moment.
오는 대로 연락해줘요
이야기 좀 해요
We need to talk.
I have some news.
알려줄 소식이 있어요
Hope you had a good night.
편한 밤 보냈길 바라요
Later.
또 만나요
팎읔襟俚캥莉
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
뻑短속흙
피드백
whemie@gmail.com